

Muhammad Mahdani R.

Front-End Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a Front End Developer. Since I first became interested in the world of technology and web design, I have been committed to becoming a professional who delivers amazing user experiences through Front-End Development.



0812-7496-7122



mahdanidn@gmail.com



Jalan Mujahidin No.365 RT.08 RW.03 Bukit Kecil Palembang



Link Portfolio

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

PT.LOKO Sistem Terintegrasi (2020-2023)

- Responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining web and mobile applications using Flutter technology, as well as integrating attractive and functional user interfaces.
- Implement the design that has been created by the UI/UX Designer as a Front-End Developer and also handle Mobile applications using the Flutter framework.

Full-Stack Developer

PT.Sinergi Mitra Groserindo (2023- Present)

- Handle their client's ongoing projects, for maintenance, feature enhancement, bug fixing.
- · Check and optimize website speed regularly.

SKILLS

- React.js
- Vue.js
- Next.js
- Nuxt.js
- Typescript
- Flutter
- Laravel

EDUCATION

2011 - 2014

SHS Srijaya Negara

2015 - Undgradued (End of Semester)

University Information Bina Darma System